I think now is a good time to tell you
all that I teach high school that's my
day job in Seattle don't worry about it
your kids are fine just high school
right out of college at 22 years old
right out of a conservative Christian
College they're like we're gonna have
you teach sex ed cuz apparently their
philosophy was those who can't you have
the lunch lady teach health class too
what's going on here
I teach world history now I teach world
history which is fun I like to teach
world history it allows me to teach the
kids about things they've never thought
of before maybe you've never thought of
this they didn't call it World War one
at the time that would've been super
pessimistic yeah well there's gonna be a
bunch of these things so uh we'll just
call this one one and we'll see what
happens right what'd they call it at the
time anybody know the Great War that's
right an HG Wells he referred to it as
the war to end all wars which didn't
work out very well right call World War
one at the time would be like if I would
have walked up to you and be like here
I'd like to introduce you to wife number
one
gonna be a bunch of these things so uh
I'm not an idiot I've she introduced her
as the great wife to be saved right and
now the wife to end all wives cuz I'm
not doing it again teaching history also
allows me to teach about race issues and
so it's very important in our country
right now I also recognize not really
the right guy to do it really super
balls super white dude mm-hmm I'm one
neck tattoo away from a hate crime right
now I mean this guy teaching your
history class no way
it's always the wrong people to get on
their high horse about race no it's
always like suburban white soccer moms
or like I just don't see color
oh that's cuz you live in Utah
[Applause]
no I don't see color I don't even see it
yes you do and it's fine to notice color
just don't judge people based on what
you see it's all no no I'm colorblind no
you're not plus that's not gonna work
cause you know you still see when you're
colorblind black and white grey being
colorblind just makes Asians gray but
you can still tell
you guys did well with that well that's
fine yeah yeah
subscribe to drive our comedy for even
more of the world's largest collection
of clean comedy